{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who was born in Bethlehem and became a prophet?",
            "category": "History",
            "answer": "Jesus",
            "answers": [
                "ceaser",
                "John the baptist",
                "Jesus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Gandhi's first name?",
            "category": "History",
            "answer": "Mohandas",
            "answers": [
                "Mohammed",
                "Mohandas",
                "Muhammad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What year was JFK assassinated?",
            "category": "History",
            "answer": "1965",
            "answers": [
                "1964",
                "1965",
                "1966",
                "1963"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Julius Caesar's grand-nephew?",
            "category": "History",
            "answer": "Augustus",
            "answers": [
                "Marc Anthony",
                "Flavius",
                "Augustus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Albert Einstein famous for?",
            "category": "History",
            "answer": "",
            "answers": [
                "Inventions",
                "Religious leader",
                "Theorist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is greater than 4",
            "category": "Math",
            "answer": "5",
            "answers": [
                "5",
                "-5",
                "-1/2",
                "-25"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the author of the famous storybook 'Alice's Adventures in Wonderland'?",
            "category": "Literature",
            "answer": "Lewis Carroll",
            "answers": [
                "Rudyard Kipling",
                "John Keats",
                "Lewis Carroll",
                "H G Wells"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who wrote the famous 1855 poem 'The Charge of the Light Brigade'?",
            "category": "",
            "answer": "Lord Alfred Tennyson",
            "answers": [
                "Lord Alfred Tennyson",
                "Christopher Marlowe",
                "Johannes Gutenberg",
                "René Descartes"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who wrote 'Where ignorance is bliss, it is folly to be wise'?",
            "category": "",
            "answer": "Shakespeare",
            "answers": [
                " Browning",
                "Marx",
                "Shakespeare",
                "Kipling"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Combine terms: 12a + 26b -4b – 16a.",
            "category": "Math",
            "answer": " -4a + 22b",
            "answers": [
                " -4a + 22b",
                "4a + 22b",
                "28a + 30b",
                "-28a + 30b"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": " Which is the smallest?",
            "category": "Math",
            "answer": "-1",
            "answers": [
                "-1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "A card is selected at random from a standard 52 card deck. Assuming all cards are equally likely to be selected, what is the probability that a red card was selected given that a king was selected?",
            "category": "",
            "answer": "1/2",
            "answers": [
                "1/26",
                "1/4",
                "1/2",
                "1/13"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "A card is selected at random from a standard 52 card deck. Assuming all cards are equally likely to be selected, what is the probability that a red card or a king was selected?",
            "category": "Math",
            "answer": "7/13",
            "answers": [
                "15/26",
                "17/26",
                "7/13",
                "1/2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "A card is selected at random from a standard 52 card deck. Assuming all cards are equally likely to be selected, what is the probability that a red king was selected?",
            "category": "Math",
            "answer": "1/26",
            "answers": [
                "1/26",
                "1/52",
                "1/13",
                "15/26"
            ]
        }
    ]
}